So, you and Rachel
tonight, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
It's actually our
first official date.
Wow, so tonight
may be the night.
You nervous?
Nah. No.
This is the part
I'm actually good at.
What must it be like
not to be crippled
by fear and self-loathing?
It's okay.
How can you be
so confident?
Well, I-I know exactly
what I'm going to do.
Really, like you
have a routine?
No, no, no, no, no.
See, each woman is different.
You have to appreciate
their uniqueness.
Really?
No, I do six things.
First, I look deep
into her eyes,
then I kiss her.
Next, I take my hand,
and I softly graze her thigh.
You mean, like this?
No, not like that.
No. No, like this.
Ah, I see
what you mean.
That's quite nice.
( clearing throat):
Foosball?
And beer.
Yeah.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to fall ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey.
Hey, sweetie.
Wow.
Hey, stop staring
at my wife's legs.
No, no.
Stop staring at
your sister's legs.
I'm sorry, it's just...
How'd you get so tan?
She went to one of those
spray-on tan places.
You got a spray-on tan?
Chandler
gets pedicures.
Wh-What, you do?
Like with
the-the toe separators?
Why? W-Why?
Still, I can't believe
that's sprayed on.
I mean, it looks really good.
I wonder if I should get one.
Sure, and then
you should get a miniskirt
so you can really show it off.
So do you get colors
or just French tips?
Here.
Here's
their card.
Thanks.
Hey, I know where this place is.
It used to be
an X-rated video...
Florist.
Hey.
Hey, Pheebs.
Hey, Phoebe.
Oh, you won't believe
who moved back to town.
I know, Amanda.
She called me, too.
She's the worst.
Who's Amanda?
She's this girl who used to live
in the building
before you did.
And then she moved to England,
and she picked up
this fake British accent.
On the machine,
this is her message:
( strange accent ):
"Monica, darling,
it's Amanda calling."
Are you trying to do
a British accent?
Chandler gets pedicures.
Just so I know, how many
more of those can I expect?
So you know what
Amanda said to me
when she got me on the phone?
( British accent ):
"Oh, so sorry to catch you
on your mobile."
If you... if you didn't want
to get me on my mobile,
then don't call me on my mobile.
I know.
And she's
always bragging
about all the famous
people she's met.
Oh, I know.
( accent ):
"Uh, I slept with Billy Joel."
All right, who hasn't?
Oh, what are we going to do?
I don't want to see her.
Oh, let's just cut her out.
What?
Cut her out of our lives.
Just ignore her calls and dodge
her till she gets the point.
Well, I-I guess
we could try that,
but it seems so harsh.
Have you ever done that?
Nope, had it done to me, though.
Feels good.
All right, Mr. Geller,
right this way.
So, how dark
do you want to be?
We have one,
two or three.
Well, uh, I like how you look.
What are you?
Puerto Rican.
Two, I think a two.
You're going
to face the red light.
When the red light goes on,
the spray's about to start,
so close your eyes.
When the spraying stops,
count to five.
Pat yourself down
to avoid drip marks,
then turn around
so we can get your back.
You got it?
Spray, count, pat and turn.
Spray, count and pat.
Wow, you catch on quick.
Well, I have a Ph.D, so...
One Mississippi, two
Mississippi, three Miss...
Wait! Wait!
I'm not...
I'm not finished counting!
You sprayed my front twice!
You never turned?
No, I barely even got
to three Mississippi.
Mississippi?
I said count to five.
Mississippi-lessly?
Well, how-how bad is it?
Not that bad,
yet,
but it keeps getting darker
for the next four hours.
So, how dark
is it going to get?
Well, you got sprayed
with two two's and...
I'm a four?
Yeah, but your back's a zero.
You're going to want
to even that out.
Really?
You might want
to get back in there.
Oh, okay.
Wait, wait a minute.
There's no light
on the back wall.
How do I know
when it's going to start?
Hello?
Ow! My eye! Ow, ah...
Ah!
( spitting )
( grunting )
The same thing
happened again.
You got two more two's?
I'm an eight!
Thanks for dinner.
I thought you paid.
Huh, guess we won't
be going back there.
( chuckles )
So...
Yeah.
Hey, what do you say
we, uh, move this
onto the likes of the couch?
I say, cheesy
line, but okay.
What's the matter?
I-I-I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I did that.
Okay.
Sorry.
I'm sorry. Again.
I don't know...
don't know what happened.
I must be nervous.
I don't get it.
Chandler loved it.
Okay.
I promise,
I promise, I promise.
I won't do it again,
I really do, I promise.
This is going to be great.
Okay.
Uh, w-was that
good for you?
( phone ringing )
No, no,
don't get it.
Let the machine
pick up.
Oh, yeah, it could be Rachel
asking if someone
could baby-sit again.
It could be Amanda.
Oh, you're right. Oh!
I was just kidding about Rachel.
Baby-sitting's a gas.
AMANDA ( on machine ):
Hello, Monica.
It's Amanda calling again.
I'm in the neighborhood
hoping I could
pop by your flat.
You're from Yonkers!
Your last name is Bouvamonteezy.
Let's see.
So should you get this directly,
ring me back on my mobile.
Okay, don't hold thy breath.
( dialing )
CHANDLER:
Hello? Is someone on the line?
AMANDA:
Yes, I-I was looking for Monica.
CHANDLER:
Hang on.
She's right here.
Someone's on
the phone for you.
We weren't picking up.
It's Amanda.
I get pedicures.
Hi, Amanda.
Uh... actually,
now is-is not a good time.
Dinner tomorrow night?
Okay, Phoebe and I
will see you then.
Why? Why?
Why didn't you just say no?
Well, I said no to her
coming over now.
I couldn't say no twice.
I've got this uncontrollable
need to please people.
Fine. Fine.
You would not hold up well
under torture.
Oh, and you would?
I did.
Uh... Rach, are you sure
you want to do this?
Absolutely. Absolutely.
I... it's just
a little weird--
it's you, and it's me.
It's just going to take
some getting used to.
Okay.
Okay, well, uh...
h-how can we
make it easier?
Okay, let's work
from the top down.
Just work the bra, Joe!
Okay, got it, yeah.
Okay.
Absolutely.
All right.
Mm.
Okay.
Okay, uh...
Mm.
This thing
welded shut?
Okay.
All right.
Turn around-- I
got to get a look
at this thing.
( sighs ):
Okay.
( snaps )
Ow!
Sorry.
Well, this is romantic.
( sighs ):
I'm sorry!
This had never
happened to me before.
I'm an expert at
taking off bras.
I can do it with one hand.
I can do it with my eyes closed.
One time, I just looked at one,
and it popped open.
I blame your bra.
It's a standard issue bra clasp.
Well, then, I blame you. Yeah.
That's right. You threw me off
with all your slappin'.
Okay, look...
Well, I'm really...
I'm sorry about that, Joey,
but do you think maybe
on-on some level,
you-you... you don't want
to take off my bra?
No, I don't have
another level!
CHANDLER:
Hold on.
There's something different.
I went to that
tanning place
your wife suggested.
Was that place... the sun?
Oh. And it gets worse.
Oh, my God,
you can do a duet
of "Ebony and Ivory"
all by yourself.
How could you
mess this up?
It's so easy.
You go into the booth,
you count to five,
and you turn around.
How do you count to five?
One, two, three...
Damn it!
( gasps )
I know!
( laughs )
Oh, what is up
with Miss Hawaiian Tropic?
How was your
date with Joey?
Well,
it was... good
until we got back
to our apartment,
and then we were fooling around,
and he started
to put his hand up my leg,
and I kept slapping it away.
You didn't like that?
Well, it wasn't just me,
all right?
He freaked out, too.
He couldn't even undo my bra.
Wow, really?
One time he just looked
at my bar, and it popped open.
I do not know
what's wrong with us.
I mean, we-we've kissed before,
and that's been great.
But this time
it was leading somewhere,
and I was very aware of the fact
that it was Joey touching me.
Well, you guys
have been friends forever.
Remember the first time
that you kissed Ross,
how weird that was?
Mm-hmm.
You couldn't
stop laughing?
You got through that.
Mm-hmm. Okay.
That's true. That's true.
We can do this.
You're right, you're right,
we can do this.
We're just going
to power through.
Hey. Ah, Chandler, can I talk
to you for a second?
No need, problem solved--
we are powering through.
Chandler, stop.
It's not going
to pop open.
You don't know.
Hi, Phoebe.
Hey.
Okay. Is Amanda here yet?
No.
Oh, good.
Hey, look, I am so sorry
for screwing up
that cutting-her-out plan,
but I have a new plan.
Chandler agreed to call here
in a few minutes
with an emergency.
Oh, well, okay, what
kind of emergency gets
us both out of here?
Well, what do you think
of Mike and Chandler
being in a car accident?
Are you kidding?
I love it!
Here she comes.
Hi!
( laughing )
Hello! Hi!
It's so nice to see you.
Both of you, look at me.
Look how young I look.
Oh, gosh, we have so
much to catch up on.
But first things first.
Touch my abs.
I don't exercise at all.
Oh, gosh.
So Monica, you're married.
Yeah. Yeah, his name
is Chandler, and he's...
Oh, smell my neck.
It's not perfume, it's me!
It's my natural scent.
M-Musty.
Oh...
Gosh, this is brilliant.
Gosh, it's just like old times.
I'm so happy
you two are friends again.
When were we not friends?
Well, it was 1992,
and I remember,
because that was
the year I had sex
with Evel Knievel.
( giggling )
Oh... uh, we were friends
in 1992.
No, I distinctly remember
you were dodging her calls
and trying to avoid seeing her.
Wait, you were going
to cut me out?
Well, kind of.
Oh, my God.
Oh, bugger.
Should I not
have said that?
Oh! I feel like a perfect arse!
Well, in America
you're just an ass.
Oh.
( cell phone ringing )
Hello?
Chandler, what's wrong?
Oh, my God,
are you all right?
Uh, yeah.
I'll be right there.
Oh, I'm so sorry,
but Chandler was
in a car accident.
Oh.
Oh, my God!
Yeah.
Was Mike with him?
Nope!
Hey!
RACHEL:
Got champagne?
Yes, ma'am.
Ready to power through.
Excellent!
Okay, stick it
in the ice bucket,
the phone is
off the hook,
and in the interest
of powering through...
Ooh... ooh!
Okay,
sexy, sexy.
Very sexy, sexy...
All right, let's do it!
Okay, okay,
you're scaring
me a little bit.
Oh, get over it, soldier,
we gotta do this!
Okay.
Okay, ha-ha,
you like that, huh?
( mischievous chuckling):
Oh, yeah!
You like that?
Let's kick this
into high gear, huh?
Oh, oh!
Ooh!
Yeah, baby, I'll show
you how we do it.
( whimpering ):
No, no, no!
You kneed me in my misters!
What?
Oh, my God!
I'm so sorry.
Joey... are you okay?
( voice cracking ):
Soldier down!
We are not friends
with Phoebe anymore.
If she asks, I protested
a little, but... okay.
( door opens )
Oh, Chandler,
thank God you're alive.
Monica, can I talk to you
outside for a minute?
I have nothing to say to you.
Wow, my flat
is twice this size. Ooh.
Please, Monica,
in the hall?
Ooh, that accident
must have been terrible!
You look positively ghastly.
Well, aren't
you a treat?
I can't believe
you tried to cut me out.
Why, Phoebe, why?
It was... it was
right after we were
living together,
and you were driving me crazy.
Okay, you were really
controlling and compulsive
and shrill.
Well, I'm still
all those things!
You're also so generous
and kind and scrappy.
I am scrappy.
Exactly.
L-Look, no matter
what I tried to do,
I couldn't keep
you out of my life.
Of all the people
I've cut out,
you were the only one who
ever clawed her way back in.
That's because I'm scrappy.
Yeah, you are,
and I'm so glad that
you fought your way back in,
because I don't know
what I would do without you.
Well, I don't know
Ah...
( Phoebe chuckles )
Well, I guess
we should go back in.
I mean, you gave me
another chance.
I guess we should
do the same for Amanda.
Yeah, I guess
you're right.
All right.
Can you believe it?
I've never had
any professional dance training.
Now, let me explain
how this works.
You go into the booth,
and you push the...
I'm going to stop you
right there, Linda.
Okay?
Does it look like
this is my first time? Huh?
Now, I want four two's,
and I want 'em all on my back.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
There's two sets of nozzles!
Which one is it?!
Which-which-which-which one
is it?
Oh...
son of a bitch!
What is the matter
with us?
Well, I know what's
the matter with me.
No...
No, I mean with us, you know?
I mean, is it supposed
to be this...
difficult?
( sighs softly )
I don't know.
That fake British woman's a real
bitch, but she sure can dance.
Hey.
Hi.
Hey, listen,
can we ask you a question?
When you and Monica
first hooked up,
was it weird going from friends
to... more than that?
Kind of. You know,
sneaking around,
having to hide from you guys.
RACHEL:
No, no, no.
No, I mean... sexually.
Yeah, uh-uh, was there a part
of you that-that felt like
it was... really wrong?
Actually, no.
No, it felt right, you know?
It felt like, uh,
"I can't believe we haven't been
doing this the whole time."
I can tell
from your expressions
that's the good news
you were hoping for.
Well, I'm going to go
continue to spread the joy.
( sighs )
Well, just because
it happened that way for them
doesn't mean it has to happen
that way for us.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
I mean, just because
something's difficult
doesn't mean that you quit.
Right, totally.
Yeah. And so
we'll just
keep trying and trying
until we... do it.
Yeah, and if
it doesn't work,
then we'll just be
one of those couples
that never has sex.
( weakly ):
That's a plan.
( sighs )
Wow...
I did not see
this coming.
I know.
I... I don't get it.
I mean,
I was so sure this
was what I wanted.
Mm-hmm.
Me, too.
( sighs contentedly )
Well, how come
Monica and Chandler could do it?
I guess they weren't as
good friends as we are.
Wow.
I bet you're right.
Mm.
So...
Yeah.
I love ya.
Love ya, too.
All right,
I'm going to bed.
Yeah, me, too.
( groaning ):
Ooh, yeah.
I'm not going anywhere
for a while.
( knocking )
Dude, it's Chandler.
Let me in.
Go away.
I don't want to see anybody.
I know.
I went to the
tanning place,
and the same thing
happened to me.
You have to let me in.
Really?!
Did you count Mississippily?
You-you're not tanned.
No, I just had to get a picture
of this.
( laughing ):
I'll see you later.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org